readersdigest.co.za 2005-04-05

# Privacy Policy

**R EADER'S DIGEST PRIVACY POLICY**  
 ** _General statement_**  
Many Internet users are unaware of how easy it is to give away information about themselves when they navigate the web. We respect and protect the privacy of our users. Reader's Digest (RD) wishes the users of its online presence to know that it seeks to comply with all elements of the Privacy Act. ** _Record of visits_**  
When you visit the RD website pages, our server makes a record of the visits and logs the user's server address, the user's top-level domain name, the date and time of visit to the site, the pages accessed and documents downloaded, the previous site visited and the type of browser used for statistical purposes. No attempt is made to identify users, or their browsing activities, unless a law enforcement agency or a court exercises a valid warrant to inspect the service provider's logs. ** _Collection of information_**  
We collect information from visitors to our site during online purchasing, sweepstakes registration, online customer service activity, and so on. The personal information we collect will typically be used by RD to offer you special promotional offers and exciting product opportunities from time to time. We may occasionally make your email address available to other carefully screened marketers who we believe have products of interest to you. Should you not wish to receive these offers, please email us to that effect.

RD makes use of "cookies" to make our website perform better. A "cookie" is a feature built into your browser that assigns you a "user ID". Cookies are used to follow the pattern of movements of web users. Cookies let us know which pages on our website are visited, in what order and how often. By themselves, cookies can't be used to discover your identity – they merely identify your computer to our servers when you visit us. If you are unhappy about having a cookie assigned to you, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. Cookies are not used to record any personal information such as your name, address or email address.

 ** _Email_**  
We will record your email address or other personal details if you send us a message, place an order with the RD Online Store, or respond to a prize or product opportunity. It will be used for the purpose for which you have provided it to RD and from time to time we may email you with promotional offers and opportunities to purchase products from us. ** _Security_**  
When you begin to place credit card details on the RD Online Store, a secure system software called "socket security layer" (SSL) encrypts all information you input before it is sent to us. ** _Information by mail_**  
Reader's Digest appreciates that some people may not wish to submit information via email or the Internet. If you do not wish to submit personal information to RD through our websites or via email, you can write to Customer Service Office, 10 Mill Street, Newlands, 7708 Cape Town. ** _How can I access information that is held in my Reader's Digest customer file?_**  
We are happy to provide you with details of information held about you on our customer file. To access this information, you need to email or write to us using the contact details below. Please also include your account number. ** _You and your privacy_**  
If you have any questions regarding any matters related to your privacy, or if you believe there has been a breach of your privacy, please contact us on: **Mailing Address:**  
21 Dreyer Street, 1st Floor, Sanclare Building, Claremont7708 Cape Town 8000, South Africa  
Email:[customer.sa@readerdigest.com](mailto:customer.sa@readersdigest.com)

Home Page| Contact Us| Subscribe Now| Global Sites| Sweepstakes Information| Online Bill Payment | Online Store| Internet Special | Win With Us | Privacy Policy| Register| 

 Copyright © 2004 Reader's Digest (South Africa) Pty Limited. All rights reserved. Unauthorized use is strictly prohibited

| 

[ **Register and win this superb**  
 **Panorama Camera**](http://www.readersdigest.co.za/cgi-bin/webc.exe/ur_registerform.html)

---|---
